<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Æ Software</title><link>https://www.andreaseisele.com/</link><description>Andreas Eisele, IT Consultant, Software Architect, Software Developer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 15:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.andreaseisele.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moving to GitHub Pages, Pt.2</title><link>https://www.andreaseisele.com/posts/moving-to-gh2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 15:49:20 +0200</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.andreaseisele.com/posts/moving-to-gh2/</guid><description>Further on Hosting Stuff with GitHub Pages Let&amp;rsquo;s repeat my ToDo list of the last blog post here and see where we are:
create blog locally add content setup github pages add github action to auto deploy update DNS zone enable comments enable share links add meaningful content Not too bad? But how did we arrive here?
Hosting under custom domain In theory that&amp;rsquo;s quite easy. Once you have GitHub Pages set up your page will already be available as username.</description></item><item><title>Moving to GitHub Pages</title><link>https://www.andreaseisele.com/posts/moving-to-gh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 23:00:12 +0200</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.andreaseisele.com/posts/moving-to-gh/</guid><description>Hosting Hugo on GitHub Pages As mentioned in my last blog post my goal was to move this entire homepage to be hosted on github pages.
TL;DR: My ToDo create blog locally add content setup github pages add github action to auto deploy update DNS zone Hugo Build The straight forward thing to turn this collection of Markdown and other resources into a proper webpage is to simply have Hugo built it.</description></item><item><title>Blogging with Hugo</title><link>https://www.andreaseisele.com/posts/blogging-with-hugo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:25:48 +0200</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.andreaseisele.com/posts/blogging-with-hugo/</guid><description>A NEW BLOG This is not my first blog ever. Over the years I&amp;rsquo;ve maintained and scrapped various personal webpages including weblogs. Now it&amp;rsquo;s time for another try. I want to focus my writing here on tech and IT in whatever one may consider to be the professional side - but who am I kidding, a blog is never strictly professional. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how this goes. 😉
The Tech Stack I have some prior experience with both maintaining and running Wordpress blogs.</description></item></channel></rss>